hi everyone this is advice routine and
i'm here to share with you kompa ano
maba maguiro from your sun life video
[Music]
[Applause]
especially if within five or ten years
balancia ideally because if you have
this plan you understood that it's an
insurance policy in the first place and
as much as possible long-term and
financial goal nothing's a savings
component
but if
you can do partial withdrawal anytime
you want to
so
while we draw partially on sunlight near
a plan
number one you can go to sun time
service center hanapin and pineham
alabama service centers
website
www.sunlife.com
then you can go to about us and click
where to find us
[Music]
to find us make sure longer you bring at
least one valid and primary id or two
secondary ids and of course the fat
allah william policy number one
number two
you can reach out to your financial
advisor in this case my papa permanent
form sayo which you can sign digitally
or petted in via email confirmation
so same with option number one hinging
and link ioni advisor now ids to support
the documents depend is a completeness
and form withdrawal requests can take
five to ten working days of effort
number three
via email request
if you don't have any sunlight financial
advisor you can still send your
completed and signed withdrawal request
form via email to sun link at
sunlight.com
but take note kelang notaries
a witness and staff or advisor from
sunlight and usually ms mata and
processing
need to verify
so to sum up this video you have three
options to withdraw from your sunlight
via plan
number one go to sunlight client service
center
number two you can reach out to your
financial advisor and number three you
can send your request via email some
other things that we have to take note
minimum withdrawal amount from your vr
account is 5 000 pesos and the
withdrawal amount is not deducted to
your face amount or accommodation
plus your vl-100 robot form should be
signed by the policy owner and commander
vocabulary features
our presence
service center
and third is your weakness
may witness someone
leave a comment below or send me a
message through my social media pages in
the description box
[Music]